


<resources>
<string name="app_name">Daily Yoga - India no.1 fitness app</string>
<string name="before_age_18">Before Age 18</string>
<string name="days_60">Days 60</string>
<string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="banner9">ca-app-pub-2979367707216609/9503016155</string>
    <string name="inter_id2">ca-app-pub-2979367707216609/8922525674</string>
    <string name="banner6">ca-app-pub-2979367707216609/9901637257</string>
    <string name="inter_ad_id">ca-app-pub-2979367707216609/7539197790</string>
    <string name="banner4">ca-app-pub-2979367707216609/8184159070</string>
    <string name="banner3">ca-app-pub-2979367707216609/6857768991</string>
    <string name="banner_id2">ca-app-pub-2979367707216609/7979310799</string>
    <string name="app_id">ca-app-pub-2979367707216609~2754038302</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-2979367707216609/7310298782</string>
<string name="after_age_18">After Age 18</string>

<string name="pose1">    Step 1:- Start in the push-up position with your arms completely straight and directly beneath your shoulders.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Your body should form a straight line from your shoulders to your ankles. \n\n
                             Step 3:- Squeeze your abs, lift one foot off the floor and bring your knee up towards your chest while keeping your body in as straight of a line as possible. \n\n
                             Step 4:- Return to the starting position and repeat the movement with your opposite leg.. </string>
<string name="pose2">    Step 1:- Lie flat on your mat with knees bent and feet on the mat. Hands at the base ofyour head and elbows pointed out. Using your abdominals bring your head and shoulders off the mat and come up into a crunch, then lower with control. </string>
<string name="pose3">    Step 1:- This movement is performed with a bench and a foot stool.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Place a bench behind yourself and rest on it with your hands. Place your legs straight out in front of you. You may also place them at an elevated level as shown above.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Begin with arms in a fully. Slowly bend at your elbows keeping the rest of your body straight. Be sure to keep your elbows back and close together.\n\n
                             Step 4:- Dip down until your arms form a 90 degree angle and you feel a stretch in the triceps.\n\n
                             Step 5:- Slowly extend your arms raising your body back up. Pause and contract your triceps muscles at the top. Pause and repeat the movement.</string>
<string name="pose4">    Step 1:- Lie flat on the floor with your lower back pressed to the ground (pull your navel in to also target your deep abs). \n\n
                             Step 2:- Put your hands behind your head, then bring your knees in towards your Chest and lift your shoulder blades off the ground, but be sure not to pull on your neck.\n\n
                             Step 3:-Straighten your right leg out to about a 4S-degree angle to the ground while turning your upper body to the left, bringing your right elbow towards the left knee.\n\n
                             Step 4:- Make sure your rib cage is moving and hotjust your elbows. Now switch sides and do the same motion on the other side to complete onerep. </string>
<string name="pose5">   Step 1:- Lay down with your hands to your sides for support. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Raise your legs so they are off the ground, keeping the abdominals tight.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Slowly raise your legs 90 degrees, contracting the abdominal muscles. Slowly return to starting position. Do not touch the floor with your feet.\n\n
                            </string>


<string name="pose6">    Step 1:- Lie on your back on an exercise mat. With your arms straight at your sides, bend your knees and place your feet flat on the floor between18 and 24 inches apart.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Breathing out, crunch your ab slightly upward and sideways to the right a couple of inches until your right hand touches your right heel.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Hold brief|y and then return to your starting position while inhaling. Repeat on the left side. </string>
<string name="pose7">    Step 1:- You can perform straight-leg crunches by lying face up on the floor with your legs straight and then moving your upper body as you would for a standard bent-knee crunch.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Alternatively, lie on your back, raise your legs so they are perpendicular to the floor and then perform the standard crunching motion with your torso.
                             </string>
<string name="pose8">    Step 1:- Lie down on the floor placing your feet either under something that Will not move or by having a partner hold them. Your legs should be bent at the kneesPlace your hands behind your head and lock them together by claspihg your fingers. This is the starting position.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Elevate your upper body so that it creates an imaginary V-shape with your thighs. Breathe out when performing this part of the exercise.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Once you feel the contraction for a second, lower your upper body back down to the starting position while inhahng. \n\n
                             Step 4:- Repeat for the recommended amount of repetitions.
                            </string>
<string name="pose9">    Step 1:- Lying on the back,lift stright leg,extend opposite hand to touch toe. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Please,return,alternate inhale down,exhale up at toe touch.
                            </string>
<string name="pose10">    Step 1:- High Plank position then slowly rotate your torso to the side raising your arm till it gets ihlihe with the other one. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Then return to the initial position.
                            </string>
<string name="pose11">    Step 1:- Lie on the floor with elbows directly beneath your shoulders and legs fully extended.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Raise your torso into the air until it makes a straight line from your shoulders to your ankles. Tighten your stomach, squeeze your butt.
                            </string>
<string name="pose12">    Step 1:- Lie down on the floor placing your feet either under something that will not move or by having a partner hold them. Your legs should be bent at the knees. Elevate your upper body so that it creates an imaginary V-shape with your thighs. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Your arms should be fully extended in front of you perpendicular to your torso and with the hands clasped. This is the starting position.\n\n
                             Step 3:- This is the starting position. Twist your torso to the right side until your arms are parallel with the floor while breathing out. \n\n
                             Step 4:- Hold the contraction for a second and move back to the starting position while breathing out. Now move to the opposite side performing the same techniques you applied to the right side. Repeat for the recommended amount of repetitions.
                            </string>
<string name="pose13">    Step 1:- Lie on your back with your knees bent, feet flat and hip width. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Lower your pelvis 2 inches from the floor. Squeeze your glutes and lift your pelvis back to bridge position.

                            </string>
<string name="pose14">    Step 1:- Lie facedown on the floor with your arms extended in front of you and your leg extended behind you. \n\n
                             Step 2:- In one movement,engage your glutes and lower back to raise your arms,legs,and chest off the floor.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Hold for a count,then slowly return to the starting position.
                            </string>
<string name="pose15">   Step 1:- Stand, extend arms 90° to sides, bend forward 90° at waist.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Looking at the floor, rotate torso to touch hand to foot, rotate for other hand. \n\n
                             Step 3:- Head will follow chest action. </string>


<!--Reasons for not growing height:-->


<string-array name="title_stroy">


    <item>Build For Muscles</item>
    <item>Consistency:Practice daily.</item>
    <item>Breathe:Focus on breath.</item>
    <item>Start slow:Progress gradually.</item>
    <item>Listen:Honor your body.</item>
    <item>Use props:Enhance comfort.</item>
    <item>Warm up/cool down:Prevent injury.</item>
    <item>Be mindful:Stay present.</item>
    <item>Breakfast:Smoothie/oatmeal.</item>
    <item>Lunch:Salad with protein.</item>
    <item>Snacks:Fruit/nuts/yogurt.</item>
    <item>Dinner:Grilled veggies + lean protein.</item>
    <item>Hydration: Water/herbal tea.</item>
    <item>Avoid:Processed foods, sugar.</item>


</string-array>

<string-array name="details_storyy">
    <item>To build muscle, focus on strength training with progressive overload, increasing weights or reps over time. Prioritize compound exercises like squats, deadlifts, and bench presses. Consume a calorie surplus with high protein intake (1.6–2.2g per kg body weight). Ensure adequate rest and recovery for muscle growth.</item>
    <item>Consistency in daily practice is key to long-term progress. Whether it’s yoga, exercise, or a healthy habit, small, consistent efforts build momentum and compound over time. Daily practice helps you develop discipline, improve skills, and achieve goals. Skipping days slows progress, while regularity fosters growth and mastery.
        </item>
    <item>Focusing on your breath calms the mind and enhances mindfulness. In yoga and daily life, conscious breathing reduces stress, improves focus, and boosts energy. Deep, slow breaths activate the parasympathetic nervous system, promoting relaxation. By connecting with your breath, you can stay grounded and present in each moment.</item>
    <item>Starting slow allows your body and mind to adapt without overwhelming them. Gradual progression builds a solid foundation, preventing injury and burnout. Whether it’s exercise, yoga, or new habits, small, consistent steps lead to sustainable growth. Patience and persistence are key to long-term success and improvement.</item>
    <item>Listening to your body means recognizing its limits and needs. Honor how you feel, whether it\'s in exercise, rest, or nutrition. Pushing too hard can lead to injury or burnout, while being mindful of discomfort ensures safe progress. Respecting your body fosters balance, healing, and long-term wellness.</item>
    <item>Using props in yoga, like blocks, straps, or cushions, can enhance comfort and support, especially for beginners or those with flexibility limitations. They help with proper alignment, deepen stretches, and make poses more accessible. Props allow you to practice safely, prevent strain, and build confidence as you progress.</item>
    <item>Warming up prepares your body for exercise by increasing blood flow and flexibility, reducing the risk of injury. A proper cool-down helps relax muscles, restore heart rate, and improve recovery. Both are essential to prevent strain, enhance performance, and promote long-term health by allowing your body to adapt safely.</item>
    <item>Being mindful means staying fully present in the moment, whether during yoga, exercise, or daily activities. It enhances focus, reduces stress, and deepens the experience. By avoiding distractions and tuning into your body’s sensations, thoughts, and breath, mindfulness fosters clarity, balance, and a deeper connection to yourself.</item>
    <item>A smoothie or oatmeal for breakfast provides essential nutrients to kickstart your day. Smoothies offer a quick, nutrient-dense option with fruits, greens, and protein, while oatmeal is rich in fiber and can be customized with toppings like nuts, seeds, and berries for sustained energy and digestion throughout the morning.</item>
    <item>A salad with protein, such as grilled chicken, tofu, or beans, offers a balanced, nutrient-rich meal. The greens provide vitamins and minerals, while the protein supports muscle repair and keeps you full longer. Add healthy fats like avocado or olive oil to boost flavor and improve nutrient absorption.</item>
    <item>Snacks like fresh fruit, nuts, or yogurt provide a healthy energy boost between meals. Fruit offers natural sugars and fiber, nuts are packed with healthy fats and protein, and yogurt is a great source of probiotics and calcium. Together, they support digestion, muscle recovery, and sustained energy throughout the day.</item>
    <item>For dinner, grilled vegetables paired with lean protein like chicken, fish, or tofu make a nutritious and satisfying meal. The vegetables are rich in vitamins, fiber, and antioxidants, while lean protein supports muscle repair and keeps you full. This balanced combination promotes health, aids digestion, and supports weight management.</item>
    <item>Hydration is essential for overall health. Drinking water keeps your body hydrated, supports digestion, and boosts energy. Herbal teas, like chamomile or peppermint, can provide additional benefits like relaxation and improved digestion. Regular hydration enhances skin health, cognitive function, and helps maintain proper body temperature and joint function.</item>
    <item>Avoiding processed foods and excessive sugar helps prevent inflammation, weight gain, and chronic diseases like diabetes. These foods are often nutrient-poor and high in unhealthy fats, salt, and added sugars. Opt for whole foods like fruits, vegetables, lean proteins, and whole grains to support overall health and well-being.</item>


</string-array>

</resources>